asustor.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy - ASUSTOR Inc.

ASUSTOR INC. (hereinafter referred to as “ **ASUSTOR** ”, “ **we/our/us** ”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We endeavour to comply with all applicable laws on privacy protection and personal data security. ASUSTOR Privacy Policy, together with any privacy-related notices or statements that contain supplementary information in connection with particular ASUSTOR products and services you are using (hereinafter referred to as “Privacy Policy”), outline our privacy practices regarding the collection, use and safeguard of your personal data through ASUSTOR products and services, both online and offline we provide. In Privacy Policy, we also outline whom we may share or disclose the collected personal data. 

If you are a child, you shall access or use ASUSTOR products and services only after your parents (or your guardian) read and agree our Privacy Policy and agree to provide your personal data to ASUSTOR.

**1\. Data that ASUSTOR collects and how ASUSTOR uses such data**

This paragraph introduces what your data may be collected by ASUSTOR and how ASUSTOR may use such data through ASUSTOR products and services. 

When you use ASUSTOR products and services (for example, ASUSTOR NAS, software, official websites and customer support services), we may need to collect certain personal data from you when you use or interact with ASUSTOR products and service.  
The following is an overview of the personal data ASUSTOR may collect and how ASUSTOR may use such collected personal data. Please be noted that we will only collect certain items of your personal data for particular purposes based on the ASUSTOR products and services you actually use. Please also be noted that what items of the personal data will be collected is varied from the nature of the products and services. Moreover, in some countries, in order to avoid wrongfully collecting and using children’s personal data, you may need to additionally provide your age or the contact data of your parents (or guardian) so that we could obtain the consent from your parents (or guardian). Furthermore, when you use ASUSTOR products and services, we may collect the following anonymous data which could not directly or indirectly identify you.  
When you use ASUSTOR products and services, you do not have to provide your personal data based on our request. However, if you choose not to provide your personal data to ASUSTOR, we may not be able to provide the corresponding ASUSTOR products and services or respond to your inquiries.  
**1.1 The personal data ASUSTOR collects**  
Personal data means any data which could directly or indirectly identify you, such as your name, email address and IP address. ASUSTOR may collect your following personal data based on your prior consent:

  1. Your true, accurate, current and complete registration data, including your e-mail address, country/region and age when you sign up for an ASUSTOR ID. Moreover, when you log in to your ASUSTOR ID, you can provide your additional personal data to edit your profile of ASUSTOR ID (for example, your address and phone number), and to enjoy ASUSTOR products and services associated with your ASUSTOR ID (for example, your product serial number for ASUSTOR product registration, articles and pictures posted and uploaded on ASUSTOR forums which may contain your personal data).
  2. Your name, mailing/shipping/billing address (including postal code), contact data, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment service data when you make a purchase of our products (for example, purchasing ASUSTOR products through the ASUSTOR Accessories Store) and paid services. Moreover, in addition to the above personal data, your product data (Ex: product serial number) may also be collected when you request for certain customer services (for example, product repair services).
  3. Your name, contact data, e-mail, gender, date of birth, product data (for example, product serial number), and a copy of your invoice (in some countries, your name, address and other personal data may be included in your invoice), when you enter our events or campaigns. The actual collected items of your personal data will vary from respective event or campaign. Moreover, if you are a winner of our event or campaign, or if you will receive giveaways from ASUSTOR, you may need to additionally provide your mailing/shipping address (including postal code) and personal data for tax declaration (for example, your residential address, ID or passport number and its copy).
  4. Your product data, such as your product serial number, IP Address, MAC Address, and other unique product identifiers may be collected when you use ASUSTOR products.
  5. Your voice, video, communication records when you contact ASUSTOR (for example, by calling to the ASUSTOR call centre, using ASUSTOR online customer service portal to have a chat with ASUSTOR, filling out online application forms on ASUSTOR’s official website and sending emails to ASUSTOR). The above voice, video and communication records may contain your personal data.

**1.2 How ASUSTOR uses your personal data**  
We may use your personal data for the purposes below:

  1. To assess and improve ASUSTOR products and services.
  2. To obtain customer feedback and to analyse the user experience for the purpose of development and evaluation of new products and services.
  3. To fulfil the sign-up process of ASUSTOR ID and to experience ASUSTOR products and services associated with ASUSTOR ID (for example, product registration and services of ASUSTOR’s forums).
  4. To provide delivery services (for example, delivering proof of purchase or invoice), software updates and technical notices for ASUSTOR products and services you purchase.
  5. To process and fulfil any subscriptions you have signed up for, including ASUSTOR newsletters to keep you up to date with the latest ASUSTOR news, promotions and upcoming events. You may unsubscribe at any time with no charge.
  6. To send you important notifications, such as communications about changes to our terms, conditions and policies. 
  7. To verify your identity, deliver event or campaign entries and rewards, contact you for event or campaign-related matters, provide cashback allowance, declare tax and provide shuttle services and cover you with insurance if it is a necessity when you enter our events or contests. 
  8. To provide you with customer support services (for example, to fulfil your product repair requests and respond to your questions), our customer care and customer satisfaction survey for user experience analysis, and to protect your rights and interests and adopt access control, we may collect your voice, video and communication records when you contact ASUSTOR and ASUSTOR offices.
  9. To provide you with personalised marketing services, for example, using third party advertising cookies to offer marketing communications and advertising that we believe may be of interest of you, or recommendation about services you may be interest in based on your use of ASUSTOR products and services.
  10. Any other purposes with your prior consent.

**1.3 The anonymous data ASUSTOR collects and how ASUSTOR uses such anonymous data**  
Anonymous data means any data which cannot directly or indirectly identify you, such as your product model, software version and date of invoice. When you use ASUSTOR products and services, we may collect the following anonymous data from you, and use such collected anonymous data for any purposes. Moreover, when the following anonymous data is connected with your personal data listed above, under such circumstances, we will also treat such anonymous data as personal data and protect such anonymous data at the same level of protection for personal data.

  1. Your log data associated with ASUSTOR products and services, such as your product model name, product name, brand name, manufacturer name, part number, type and version of hardware and operation system, factory-default settings, activation time, firmware update data (for example, the execution method for firmware update, update date and result of update), size of memory and storage, Read-Only Memory (ROM) related data (for example, type, version, build fingerprint and build description of ROM), camera resolution, product colour, the telecom and network you use to connect to our products and services, the status of the network, telephony log data, standby status, crash history, preferred interface, type, version and language settings of browser, diagnose and usage data, your usage behaviour and local time.
  2. Your application data associated with your usage and interaction with ASUSTOR applications and software, such as the name and version of applications and software, the install and uninstall time, frequency and numbers of your usage, open and close time of applications and software, the category of your preferred applications and software, usage behaviour settings, update version and update result.
  3. Your purchase data of ASUSTOR products and services (for example, the purchase date and reseller’s name) when you request for certain customer support services (for example, product repair services) or join our events.

**2\. Retention of your personal data**

This paragraph introduces how long ASUSTOR retain your personal data. 

We will retain your personal data for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is permitted by law or required to fulfil other necessary purposes. For example, for customer relationship management purposes, we may retain your personal data within an adequate and reasonable period of time; to comply with tax laws or other laws and regulations. We may retain your personal data within the period requested by such laws and regulations; to follow requests from governments or judiciary for purposes such as investigation or lawsuit, we may retain your personal data for longer than the retention period. Moreover, if you wish to withdraw your previous consent to collect your personal data from ASUSTOR, we will stop collecting your personal data by your request and will only retain your personal data collected before such request for withdrawal.

**3\. To whom ASUSTOR discloses your personal data**

This paragraph introduces ASUSTOR may share your personal data to third parties under limited circumstances and purposes. 

Your personal data will not be disclosed to any third parties without one of the following exceptions:  
**3.1 Your Consent**

  * We will only disclose or share your personal data to other third parties with your prior consent.

**3.2 Business Partners**

  * We may disclose hashed and anonymous data to our business partners, for example, business partners who provide data analytics services or advertisings and marketing communications based on the hashed and anonymous data through third party advertising cookies.

**3.3 Service Providers**

  * We may disclose and share necessary items of your personal data to our service providers that provide services for or on behalf of us, for instance, marketing agencies assisting us with sending marketing communications and holding marketing events/campaigns, forwarder companies delivering repaired and purchased products to you, payment service providers processing your billing, and customer service providers offering customer support services (for example, product repair services, services through ASUSTOR’s call centre and ASUSTOR online customer service portal) to you. These service providers shall only use your personal data in compliance with our instruction and with the scope of the purposes hereof; ASUSTOR ensures that all of our service providers strictly comply with the Privacy Policy.

**3.4 For legal, protection, security purposes**  
We may disclose or share necessary items of your personal data with third parties for one of the following legal or security purposes:

  * To the extent it is required by applicable laws or regulations or competent governmental or judicial authorities, necessary to establish or preserve a legal claim or defence, or necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.
  * To protect the rights, property or safety of ASUSTOR, our service providers, customers or the public, as required or permitted by law.

**4\. Cross-border processing of your personal data**

This paragraph introduces ASUSTOR may transfer your personal data to different countries under the premises that ASUSTOR should comply with privacy-related laws and regulation in such countries. 

You understand and consent that when you agree to provide your personal data to ASUSTOR, your personal data may transferred, stored, used or processed at ASUSTOR and any of its affiliated entities, service providers who may be located in a different country to you. All said transfer, storage, or process of your personal data, shall be subject to the Privacy Policy and applicable laws on privacy protection and personal data security.

**5\. Cookies and similar technologies**

This paragraph introduces how ASUSTOR and third parties use cookies and similar technologies on ASUSTOR products and services, and how you can manage cookies settings. 

ASUSTOR and our third party partners use cookies (cookies are small text files placed on your products to personalise your user experience on ASUSTOR products and services) and similar technologies such as web beacons to provide our products and services to you. When you visit one of our websites under ASUSTOR’S website domain (including microsites and versions of particular country/region), such ASUSTOR website may use some or all of the following cookies and similar technologies.  
Almost all of the data collected through cookies will only be stored in your products, rather than being transmitted to ASUSTOR. Only under a very few and limited circumstances, your data collected through cookies may be shared to ASUSTOR. For example, when you purchase our products on ASUSTOR Store, we may use cookies to collect your IP addresses at both times when you log in and place an order on ASUSTOR Store, to verify the user who places the order is the same one who logs in ASUSTOR Store for the security of online purchase.

**5.1 How we use Cookies**  
1\. In order to enrich and perfect your online experiences, we use the following cookies which are essential to ASUSTOR products and services:

Function  | 

Example  
  
---|---  
  
Sign-up and authentication

| 

We use cookies to store your unique sign-up ID number and authentication data on your products. Cookies allow you to visit and move from page to page within ASUSTOR products and services without having to log in again on subsequent visits, such as a cookie provided by ASUSTOR.  
  
Storing your preferences and settings

| 

We use cookies to maintain your settings and preferences on your products, such as your preferred language, location or fonts; by storing the settings in cookies, it is not a necessity to reapply your preferences and settings each time you visit our products and services, such as current site cookies and Entry Page cookies provided by ASUSTOR.  
  
User-input function

| 

We use cookies to temporarily store the data you insert on ASUSTOR products and services, such as count cookies provided by ASUSTOR. For example, when you enjoy your shopping experiences through ASUSTOR Store, such cookies will help you to remember the product and the quantity you click and the data you insert.  
  
Security

| 

We use cookies to protect the security of your online purchase activities, such as IP address cookies provided by ASUSTOR. For the above purpose, when you purchase our products through ASUSTOR Store, we may store your IP addresses in ASUSTOR in order to help us verify the user who places the order on ASUSTOR Store is same as the one who logging in ASUSTOR Store.  
  
Load balancing function

| 

We use cookies for load balancing function to provide you with the stable browsing experiences on our websites, such as BIGipServerNew cookie provided by ASUSTOR.  
  
2\. For analytics purpose and to provide you with personalised advertising services and other functions, we use the following cookies to optimise your experiences in using ASUSTOR products and services:

Function  | 

Example  
  
---|---  
  
Analytics

| 

We use cookies to count the number and length of your visit in ASUSTOR products and services as well as which part or features you visit the most as well. This data helps us analyse the performance and operation of ASUSTOR products and services to improve performance and develop new features, functions and services, such as MIGO cookies provided by MIGO Corp., Google Tag Manager cookies and Google Analytics cookies provided by Google Inc. For the above purposes, when you browse our websites, we may store your personal data such as IP address and your ASUSTOR Member ID in ASUSTOR through the above MIGO cookies.  
  
Targeting and advertising

| 

We use cookies to collect data about your use in ASUSTOR products and services and identify your interests, such as the advertisings you have viewed.  
Such cookies are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaigns. ASUSTOR place cookies by using advertising campaign services, such as Hubrus DSP provided by Hubrus, Google AdWords cookies and Google Double Click cookies provided by Google Inc. These data cookies are only used between ASUSTOR and advertising campaign service providers.  
  
Watching YouTube videos embedded in our websites

| 

We use cookies to help us insert YouTube videos into our websites. You can watch YouTube videos through our websites with such cookies provided by Google Inc.  
  
**5.2 How to manage cookies settings**

  1. Please note that you can configure cookies settings by accessing the browser you install to accept, block or delete some or all of cookies (for example, third party cookies).
  2. In some countries, for the first time you browse ASUSTOR websites, we may put a brief introduction on how we use cookies in a banner placed on the top side of such ASUSTOR websites. You may freely choose to accept or block the above third party cookies through such banner.
  3. If you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of ASUSTOR products and services.
  4. The functions of cookies settings may vary depending on the type and version of browser you install. We try to list common and widely-used types of browsers as following. You may refer to the following linkage to understand how to control your cookies settings through such browsers (The content in the following linkage is English. For your easier reading, please find the language option in the following linkage to select your preferred language). Also, if you do not use anyone of the following browsers, or the content in the following linkage is removed or not accessible, please visit those browsers’ privacy-related statements or support pages for further information. You may also refer to <https://www.aboutcookies.org/> (the content in this linkage is English) which introduces how to manage your cookies settings through various browsers.

  * How to control your cookies settings through Google Chrome browser:  
<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>
  * How to control your cookies settings through Microsoft Internet Explorer browser:  
<https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer>
  * How to control your cookies settings through Mozilla Firefox browser:  
<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>
  * How to control your cookies settings through Apple Safari browser:  
[https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=zh_TW&viewlocale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=zh_TW&viewlocale=en_US)

**5.3 Web Beacons**  
A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic 1x1 (pixel) GIF or PNG image that is implemented on websites or in an email to measure the effectiveness of campaigns. ASUSTOR or our service providers may use web beacons to know if you visit certain pages or click links in ASUSTOR products and services. We may implement web beacons in our marketing communications such as eDMs or ASUSTOR newsletters to know which communication contents you have clicked or read. We will use the data from web beacons to improve our websites and ASUSTOR products and services.

**6\. Third-party links in ASUSTOR products and services**

This paragraph introduces when you visit any links or use any services provided by third parties, please always refer to privacy-related statements issued by third parties. 

ASUSTOR products and services may contain links to third-party websites. Please be aware that ASUSTOR is not responsible for the security, the privacy practices and the materials of those third-party websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our websites, and to read the privacy statements of those third-party websites carefully. This Privacy Policy applies to ASUSTOR products and services only.

**7\. Security**

This paragraph introduces how ASUSTOR protects your personal data and provide some suggestions on how to protect your personal data at your end. 

We take precautions to protect your personal data against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. We conduct internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and technical and organizational security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store your personal data. Transmission of personal data between different locations of ASUSTOR and its affiliated entities is performed through our secured wide area network. When you submit your personal data to us, your personal data is protected both online and offline. However, ASUSTOR cannot guarantee perfect security on the internet. To protect your personal data from unauthorised access, we recommend that you: 

**7.1 To appropriately protect your ASUSTOR ID, for example:**

  1. To use alphanumerical passwords when signing up ASUSTOR ID.
  2. To use your own account name and password to log in ASUSTOR ID. Also, you are solely and entirely responsible for securing the confidentiality of your account name and password and for any and all activities that occur under your ASUSTOR ID.
  3. To change your ASUSTOR ID password on a regular basis.
  4. To immediately contact us when you find that the account name/password of your ASUSTOR ID had been misappropriated. ASUSTOR may suspend or terminate the permission to login your ASUSTOR ID with such account name/password (or any part thereof), and remove your personal data related to your ASUSTOR ID.

**7.2 To keep your products up to date by applying the latest available security updates for your software and use such tools as virus/spyware scanners.**  
**7.3 If you become aware of a technical vulnerability affecting ASUSTOR products and services, please do not hesitate to contact us through**[ **privacy@asustor.com**](mailto:privacy@asustor.com) ****

**8\. How to manage your personal data**

This paragraph introduces that if you may have any inquiries or requests on your personal data collected by ASUSTOR, you may log in your “ASUSTOR Account” or manage privacy-related settings on particular ASUSTOR products and services you use. Also, you may contact us through email [privacy@asustor.com.](mailto:privacy@asus.com)

**8.1 ASUSTOR ID**

  1. Please provide your email to ASUSTOR as your ASUSTOR ID so that ASUSTOR can provide you with the corresponding ASUSTOR products and services.
  2. You may view and change your account data by logging in your ASUSTOR ID and editing your account data.
  3. If you would like to subscribe or unsubscribe ASUSTOR eDM and notice with ASUSTOR news, latest products and services, you may change the setting by logging in your ASUSTOR ID account.

**8.2 ASUSTOR products and services**  
You are free to choose to enable or disable sharing your personal data with ASUSTOR through privacy-related settings in particular ASUSTOR products and services at all times when you use such ASUSTOR products and services.

**8.3 Cookies settings (Please refer to “How to manage cookies settings” and “Cookies and similar technologies” in this Privacy Policy.)**

  1. You can manage cookies settings through the browser you install to accept, block or delete some or all of cookies (for example, third party cookies) or adopt other settings at all times.
  2. If you do not wish ASUSTOR to provide you with personalised marketing services and advertisement through third party cookies, you may block or delete third party cookies through your browser at all times.

**8.4 Contact ASUSTOR to manage your personal data**  
Your may contact us through email [privacy@asustor.com](mailto:privacy@asustor.com) as well as through ADM if you have any requests and inquiries about your personal data under your ASUSTOR ID, such as request for access, correction, download, block, deletion, objecting ASUSTOR from using some or all of your personal data (for example, you may contact us if you consider ASUSTOR is wrongfully collecting and using your personal data) and restrict ASUSTOR from using your personal data under some certain circumstances (for example, you may contact us if you do not wish your personal data to be analysed at all times.)

Also, if you have consented ASUSTOR to collect your personal data through ASUSTOR products and services, you are free to withdraw your consent by changing privacy-related settings in particular ASUSTOR products and services (please refer to 8.2 in this Privacy Policy) or by submitting your request for withdrawal of consent to us. We will stop collecting your personal data and will only retain your personal data collected before such request for withdrawal.

**8.5 Whenever you use ASUSTOR products and services, we strive to maintain the accuracy of your personal data and protect your personal data against any accidental or malicious destruction. We will accommodate your requests regarding your personal data; however, we may not be able to fulfil your above requests in one of the following circumstances:**

  1. As required or permitted under application laws;
  2. For legitimate business purposes;
  3. Unreasonably repetitive requests that require disproportionate technical efforts and resources, for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing the current practices;
  4. Potentially risks on the privacy of others;

**9\. Children’s Privacy**

This paragraph introduces that in order to protect children’s privacy, if you are a child, please seek your parents (or guardian)’s consent before you provide your personal data to ASUSTOR. Also, if your parents (or guardian) would like to manage your personal data, he/ she may contact us through email [privacy@asustor.com](mailto:privacy@asus.com)

We do not knowingly collect personal data from a child below the age of eighteen (18), or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without parental consent. We encourage parents (or guardians) to take an active role in a child’s online activities and interests while using ASUSTOR products and services.  
If you are a child, please seek parental consent before your use of ASUSTOR products and services. You may submit your personal data with parental (or guardian’s) consent to us only. Your parents (or guardian) can contact us through email to _privacy@asustor.com_ as well as through ADM to revoke or withdraw any consent previously given, request for access, correction, download, block, deletion, objecting ASUSTOR from using some or all of your personal data (for example, your parents (or guardian) may contact us if he/she considers ASUSTOR may wrongfully collect and use your personal data) and restricting ASUSTOR from using your personal data under some certain circumstances (for example, your parents (or guardian) may contact us if he/she does not wish your personal data to be analysed) at all times.

**10\. Sensitive Personal Data**  
ASUSTOR will never ask you to provide sensitive personal data such as data about your medical or health records, political, religious or philosophical beliefs, criminal offences (alleged, or committed), criminal conviction background, racial or ethnic origin, trade union membership, sexual orientation, sexual history, behaviour or genetic data. Please refrain from providing us with such sensitive personal data.

**11\. Changes to ASUSTOR Privacy Policy**  
We may change the Privacy Policy from time to time, we highly recommend you periodically review the Privacy Policy posted on our websites. By accessing or using our products and services after the Privacy Policy has been updated, ASUSTOR will deem that you consent to the Privacy Policy, including any updates. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will always be available on this page; a prominent notice such as email notification will be delivered to you about any significant changes. You can always check the “updated time” at the bottom for the most current version of Privacy Policy.

**12\. Contacting Us**  
If you have any inquiries, questions, comments or complaints about the Privacy Policy, or if you believe that ASUSTOR did not comply with the Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. If you consider we may not appropriately deal with any issues related to your personal data collected by ASUSTOR, please be noted that it is your right to lodge a complaint with government authorities handling personal data protection in your country.
